<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FreeFireGuides</string>
    <string name="how_to_install">Enter the Google Play Store then type Free Fire in the Google Play Store search field\nInstall Free Fire\nTap on the Install button and wait for the download process to complete\nHow to Play Free Fire Game After Installation\nOpen the Free Fire game application that was successfully installed on your Android phone. After opening the Free Fire online game application you will be presented with an access\ndescription.Such as access to user accounts login information updates voice chat and more. You just tap on the Confirm button.\nChoose Free Fire Login Method\nHere you can choose the login method according to what you want. Caragame.id recommends logging in using Facebook because there you can meet other friends.\nLogin using Facebook account\nEnter your email or mobile number then your Facebook password. Next tap on the Continue as button.\nSelect the gender of the character\nYou can choose the gender of the character FEMALE as female and MALE as male.\nStart playing Free Fire\nNow if you have done the steps above now you can start playing the Free Fire game by tapping on the START button</string>
    <string name="tutorial">Play with Strategy\nFree Fire game is survival where you have to survive as long as possible in order to win the game. Therefore, you must apply a special strategy so as not to fall at the beginning of the game. Playing aggressively by attacking the enemy is indeed interesting and tense.\nUnderstanding Role\nIf you play in a team or squad, then understanding the role is mandatory. In the Free Fire game, there are 4 roles, namely Sniper, Marksman, Breacher, and Support. Each role has its own complementary role and function.\nWearing a Skin that Supports Adding Rate of Fire\nOne of the important elements in the Free Fire game is the skin. If you have a lot of skins, theres nothing wrong with using a skin that can increase the Rate of Fire. The addition of the Rate of Fire will allow your shot to hit the enemy even though the damage is not too big.\nUsing Melee Weapons\nYou must know how to choose a Free Fire weapon. Melee weapons are very beneficial for players, especially when running to avoid enemy fire. Using this weapon allows your speed to increase even more when compared to pistols or firearms.\nTake advantage of Grenades\nDont focus too much on shooting weapons because you can also use grenades as weapons that are no less powerful. In fact in the Free Fire game grenades are very useful. The explosion from the grenade will knock the enemy out of hiding so you know where to shoot.</string>
    <string name="cheat">The FF or Free Fire cheat has returned again called the Novuz VIP Mod Menu Apk, the latest version. Yups, this cheat is viral because a lot of gamers have uploaded tutorials on how to use it on their Youtube channel.\nNot only that, but the channel of the owner of the Novuz apk also has a lot of views because of the posting of a video that explains about this application. Well, for you friends, toraccino, you can read the full article about Novuz FF here.\nThe Garena Free Fire game is a Battle Royale genre that is always viral with the latest news every day. In fact, every week there is always news about the Free Fire game, starting from events, sharing redeem codes, bundles, and auto Headshot or auto Aim cheat applications.\nThe auto headshot or aim cheat in the Free Fire game has a lot of applications, a few months ago Bellara VIP became the flagship apk regarding free fire cheats. And this season, another application for cheating tricks called Novuz VIP.\nWhat is Novuz FF Apk?\nNovuz Free Fire is an FF game cheat application that has been modified with additional mod menu features. So that in it there are lots of cheating tricks, as a result any FF player who installs it will easily get booyah or win.\nNovuz FF is actually the same cheat method as config auto headshot or config ff auto aim. However, the difference is if the Novus Apk Free Fire is unified in the form of an application. So that it is enough to download only one application, users can enjoy all hacking or cheating techniques.</string>
    <string name="community">Reported from Boyah! Elhaya, with the closure of the Free Fire Community Tournament site, the only way to get a Custom Room Card is in the in-game Shop.\nRegarding the differences in Custom Room Cards, Elhaya also knows that there is no difference in terms of appearance from the Custom Room Cards in the in-game Shop with the official Custom Room Cards from Garena.\nIn closing, Elhaya advised that Garena did not close the door on suggestions from players for the progress of the tournament or even from the Free Fire Community Tournament website itself.\n”For the time being, the website will be deactivated, but it is possible to reopen it with a new format, could other means be possible? And, Survivors might be able to give us input on what content is interesting to discuss on the new Free Fire Community Tournament website if we relaunch it, he concluded.</string>
</resources>